Wow brother wow two seater vehicle in yellow colour b
what a scam the policy bazaar people have done here
they did not tell that the policy
is cashless so here is the third service
aid job card do get your bike's RTI done
I saw many people saying that the timing was
changing you should get it opened for that in
which my L dep cover was there get your
insurance renewed timely
so you will remember I
told you some time ago that if you love your bike, you take
care of it then get
its service done timely and today
I am saying this that friend this thing
feels very bad I am saying it with understanding friend it
feels bad brother you people also know friend so
hello ji good morning and solid salute to all the
members of my S Triple R wherever you are, however you are
brother please accept our greetings the
thing is such that today we are
going
for the third service of our gramon and
I could not have expected that the third service would be done in such a short interval
I will show you the meter reading right now
this is going on brother  4425 which is
nothing as per one year yes let me
also tell you that it has been one year since our Gramman
so it is our anniversary too so today is the same thing
so happy anniversary to us as a
user I am
feeling a little bad today because friend the bike is
not driven so spending money on it
feels a bit strange even my family
members have started saying that brother don't ride your bike by
staying there at the showroom and getting it serviced there
because it has been one year so there are many
such things which have also expired
our insurance is about to become due so
we have to get that covered up
plus we have to get its PUC certificate also there are
some such things related to insurance
which I will share let's go and
talk about the rest in today's moto blog
brother the sun god is very bright bright bright
so the summer season has already
arrived it is 8:00 in the morning and it
seems that who knows what the
temperature is going to do to us the whole
day today  It is very hot in Delhi, they are
saying that there will be some changes in the weather
because the temperature of Delhi will go up a little more, so
brother, Delhiites, be careful, be cautious,
drink water, stay at home,
oh my god service, what a great car we saw this morning
not even on the roads of Delhi but on the Ghaziabad
border,
oh my god oh my god pash, wow
brother, wow this two seater car in yellow color
looks so hot, friend, it looks so hot
brother, well there is no comparison to our GT,
brother, those who like cars like cars, come on
brother, let's say bye to
this, the service people told me that
brother, come quickly, you will get it
serviced in the first lot today, the
main thing today is insurance,
insurance, friend, I have been so disturbed for almost a week,
I have been so
disturbed that brother, they guide me so wrongly,
these insurance people
guide me so wrongly, I have tried the policy market
also, I have tried personal agents
also, I have tried all the agents, I
mean, agents everywhere  There is so
much misguidance, even
on sites like Policy Bazaar, the meaning is not clear at
all, let's talk about all those things in the second
part of the blog, but let me tell you
that friend, get your insurance renewed timely,
many of you are going to get your bikes
insured, everyone gave a
shout out, so it is my duty to
tell you that brother, your
insurance is going to be due, I am
not an insurance agent, are you
serious, but as a friend I am telling you, get it done
timely,
you get a lot of benefits from it, plus
getting insurance is very important, today
first we go to SA Riders, which is our
best service station, I have just got
all my services done there, we go there and
put the number and sit and
talk comfortably and calmly,
put it on the side, yes, let's put it on the side, yes, so today
we are at number one and the way
I have ridden today, I know
that I have ruined even the hyper ride
today, brother, from Delhi, that is, from my home to
here  It takes about half an hour to reach Vijayanagar
and I covered that distance
in 15 minutes today. Jai Hind friends, I am enjoying
riding the bike. I do
n't feel there is any major issue with the bike. I haven't even ridden it
that much. I don't tamper with anything in
front of you guys. I don't tamper with the engine etc.
I have seen many people getting the timing change
sound, so
I would recommend that friends, don't get it opened.
Whatever YAL E-Field bikes are there, there are some
noises in them and if
you keep riding with those noises, then the
engine will respond very well. I have
some friends who have ridden a lot. Let's go
royalenfield.com.
Now let's see
what we get done with the job card. No one has come yet.
Look, it is lying empty. It is completely empty.
Your bike will be parked there. Let's go,
okay, let's see what happens
and what the expenses are. The expenses are very high.  So
guys, here is the third
service estimator job card. It will cost ₹420. There will be an
engine oil change, an oil filter
change, a chain clean, and a loop. I mean, everything is the
same, it's all basic stuff, and
because of the warranty, we won't have to get it done. Let's get it done
and get out of here quickly.
Our bike is in trouble,
and all the work that needs to be done is a normal service. So
this blog will be
similar to the previous service blog, so
if you want to see it, you can go there and
check it out. But I
saw something different, let me show you.
Look,
man, I got scared looking at the camera. So, what is happening here,
for my brothers who are working at the showroom, the engine buffing, that is, the engine cleaning
work, was going on
properly at the showroom.
Brothers have been busy for quite some time. I saw it, so
if you guys want to get it done from the showroom, you can get it done. Let's get the
service done quickly and
leave. I'll make a small shortcut, so you
can check it out. If you want to
see about the third service,  Let's
hope the work gets done quickly, brother, the
insurance people are sitting there worried, so many
calls are coming, get it done, get it done, let's
see, wherever the best suits you, we will get it done from
there.
[Music]
So guys, while the servicing work is taking time, let's
talk about the
second part of our log, which is
insurance. Let's start with the
previous insurance, which I got for
my bike through the company when
I bought the bike, that is, in maximum cases, the
company people will do it for you guys. The
insurance they gave me was something like
24,485, in which
my condition got worse, I said that if there is
so much insurance, then every
year I will be in trouble, but
fortunately I came to know that out of that, the
amount of ₹1,1117 that you are checking out,
this amount is for third party
insurance, which is
covered for 5 years. The policy was taken out by the Government of India, in it it was mentioned
that brother, the third party insurance  Party insurance is
only for 5 years if you buy a new bike,
then that case is
already insured in my bike, so I got a
lot of relief that this time my
insurance will be limited to ₹ 4000, so
I was also very happy brother, I said let's get
this work done today, we will get it done quickly,
and in the process of getting it done, that date came to an
end, now let me show you
what I did, after that I went straight to Policy
Bazaar because a normal person would do the same,
brother, Policy Bazaar is a very reputed company
and all the work is done online,
transfer etc. everything because I did
not have any claim nor did my date get
accident, there was no issue of photography as of now,
so I went straight to Policy
Bazaar, see friend, this is the layout of Policy Bazaar,
in this I have just
selected the option of zero tap, then
they increased my ID value to ₹ 39000, but the
total, like if we get it done from United, then
this value is coming, the premium of 886  It is
coming in this, I have
not taken any no claim bonus, so I will add it on.
No claim bonus is basically
given in the first year at 20%, so if I have
not taken any claim, then I can add it
to my benefits. But
what scam did the policy bazaar people do here? They did
not tell whether the policy is cashless or not.
What is a cashless policy basically? When
you take a claim, in some cases,
you do not have to pay any money in your cashless policies, and in the
policies which are not cashless, you have to pay the money first,
after that a
cheque will come in your account or the money will come through NEFT.
These people from the policy bazaar have not clarified that thing at all.
I also spoke to their director,
he said that the government companies are
not cashless, and the
private companies are cashless.
Now I will get it done through a private company, understand,
I will show you, see, for example, I had
selected the option of RO Dep,
see here, no private company is
coming in this. Oriental Insurance
United  And this is a company called IFF,
its ID value itself is giving very less, I will
not get it done at all, I
selected own damage without zero dep here,
so there is no such company through them,
one is Liberty General Insurance and
what happens is that you will get 100% claim
and on batteries and alloys and tyres
you will get a claim of 50%, so it becomes
very important to get zero dep add-on, brother,
very important, now brother my mind is confused,
what did I do after this, I talked to Royal Effi people,
I will show you their quotation also,
they made a quotation for me of
7774 in which my l dep cover was there and that means
RTI etc. which I wanted to get done is
not there, should I tell you RTI, so RTI is
return to invoice, in that if your bike gets
stolen then
you get the claim for the original value of the bike in the invoice, that was
not added, so if
I had got it added further then there would have been another add-on of
50% or  It would have increased to around ₹00 and
this is the cashless policy, you would have got a discount in it, that is, what I am getting is
around ₹7000 adding GST,
so brother, I asked the same from the other showroom,
I will show you the quotation of that as well,
look,
brother, they have played a trick, now this
policy that they have made for me is from an
ICICI Ilder company
and their premium batter, after adding everything,
RTI and LDEP, is charging ₹
7300.25, that is, I will have to spend the same ₹5000000
on the insurance policy, so
our work is done, okay, we will close this thing today
because it is almost almost
complete, the service of the bike is
also complete, let's go
brother, let's see how your bike looks,
come on, so bye, one more service has been done for our customer,
some good service is good, the
thing about this here is that
brother, you can get your bike serviced while standing in front of you,
and there is enough space for the bike as well  That's
why I prefer to get the
service done here. There was nothing special in the service.
Normal engine oil change and
oil filter change. No air filter required. Rest, after
polishing, it
shines like a
brand new bike from the showroom. So
look brother, this absolutely shining bike is in
front of you. Let's leave from here. After this we will get the
PUC done. We will get our pollution control
certificate. Brother, it has been a year, so we will have to take
care of all these things. Aa ha ha
ha, what a start, has it started? Let's hand over the
gate pass to uncle. Here, sir,
thank
you. Aa ha ha ha ha, Dhoop brother, the AC was running inside
and after coming out, it feels like I have entered a
furnace. Come on, come on, come on, let's take it out slowly. It's
smooth brother. The clutch is smooth. The
smoothness increases when your engine
oil is changed. Oh, it's
fun to drive after the service.
And when you get it done at such a good service center and you get
expert people, then there is no
problem. The braking is also perfect.
After washing, it happens a little bit that the
brakes do not work, but it's okay.  It's going well, I'm
enjoying it, let's go from here, I have to get the PUC
done, after that the main work is brother, I will get the
insurance done
and there will be expenses brother, 2272 have been spent here
on insurance, let's see how much it costs,
I will get the best for my bike, whatever is best, even if the
price goes up and down a little, but I will get the best thing for my
bike, come on brother, let's go straight home, so guys,
finally my insurance is done today, after getting
tired and fed up, I got the insurance done
and it is also necessary brother, getting insurance,
now get your bike insured, it is
very important, I got this thing done from Bajaj Ayan,
which was my last year's
company, I had also tried ICICI,
but the U/N quotation
that was coming, the value
of my bike was coming out was very less and the value they were
claiming was coming out was very high, that is,
their premium was coming out too high,
my RTI was also covered in this policy,
I also got a cashless policy, I also
got a no claim bonus, plus plus plus
my insurance is zero  If it is a dep then
what else did I need in life, everything is
covered up in it, after paying its premium,
I have got a total policy of around 7000, it
is a bit expensive but I would
suggest you guys to also
invest in such a policy for your bike
because because your GT,
many people's GT came after my GT,
so I would suggest all my friends to
definitely get an RTI done for their bike,
when you are getting insurance done, there is a very
good clause, many people do not know about it
and many people do not get it done, but personally
I would suggest that you get it done for 3 years, that
is, this clause will be valid for 3 years
for your bike and it will be renewed every year,
so the cost of its policy will be charged
separately, many
things are covered in 7000 and that's it, now the
insurance is done, the pollution is done, finally
I can celebrate my grandmother's anniversary with me, it's been
a year brother,
now this is that we did not do any special celebration, but hope we will do it  All we will do is
proceed quickly,
do some long rides and grow our channel,
brother, I have a dream of 5k, I want to fulfill it, if
you want to get it done then get it done quickly, hope fully
you must have cleared
all your doubts related to insurance and pollution certificate by now, as to
where did the fly come from, if you still have any doubt then
definitely tell me in the comment section,
I will try my 100% and reply to you, so let's
keep this blog here, we will
meet soon in the next blog with some new
adventure, till then take care, tata,
bye-bye and love you all, I really need to sleep a little, I am
not able to sleep properly, so let's
complete my sleep.